HTML & CSS





AMAR NATH YOGI

OBJECTIVE

Quite skilled in developing Progressive Web Apps using Javascript & React & Backend Server using Python & Flask/Django. I am also a fluent communicator & a quick learner. I aim at getting hired on a job where I can put my skills & traits to ensure being a profitable hire for my employer, simultaneously expanding my own professional experience & horizon by adding new tools to my arsenal.

EDUCATION

B.E. in "Computer Science & Engineering"

Aug 2015 - May 2019

CGPA: 8.05

University: R.G.P.V., Bhopal

College: Jai Narain College Of Technology, Bhopal

12th 10th

July 2014 - March 2015July 2012 - March 2013Percentage: 71%Percentage: 81.16%Certificate: I.S.C.Certificate: I.C.S.E.

School: Fatima Convent H.S. School, Nagda

PERSONAL DETAILS

Nagda(M.P), India

+917693060897

@ nathyogiamar@gmail.com

www.cyogian.dev

SKILLS

A Linux

Python

Js JavaScript

☐ Flask/Django

5 HTML

 CSS

Sass SASS

MySQL & MongoDB

EXPERIENCE

Stride.AI (Jul 2021 - Present)

Building & Maintaining Frontend UI/UX, Progressive Web Apps for Custom Products based on Process Automation related to official documents such as KYC, Bank Documents, financial documents, etc

Building and maintaining Company's Official Website.

Stack: Javascript, React, Redux, Axios, PDF.JS, Material UI, Semantic UI, HTML, CSS₃, D₃, MongoDB

LateralX (Jun 2019 - Jun 2021)

Building & Maintaining AR & VR Embedded Web Applications.

Stack: Javascript, React, Redux, Axios, HTML, CSS3, Semantic UI, Google VR View, Vectary, React360, Python, Flask, FastAPI, SQL

ፙ git & GitHub

Gatsby/JamStack

REST API

GraphQL API

B MaterialUI React

SemanticUI

D3

Webpack

Babel

Firebase & Firestore



NOTE

Do check my Portfolio
Site at
www.cyogian.dev
to get a more detailed
view of my Skillset.

PROJECTS

Bancobase (July 2021 - October 2021)

A Single Page Application that has cookie based authentication & session management, a dashboard to see general information, a detailed list of uploaded files with search, sort, etc. Also has an interface for user to upload pdf files. A results page where one can view the extracted datapoints & mark new values for datapoints.

Stack: JavaScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, MaterialUI, MomentJS, PDF.js, React PDF Highlighter

Amar's Portfolio (Oct 2020 - Jan 2021)

A portfolio site which exhibits a Home Page with a brief intro, a Technologies Page with detailed list of Technology Stack & tools and a Projects Page. Deployed on Netlify, this site itself shows off my skills in developing responsive sites

Stack: JamStack, Gatsby, React, Javascript, FontAwesome

Microblog UI (Feb 2020 - Present)

A react based Single Page Application that uses Flask based RestAPI as backend. This application has features such as creating & deleting post, login/logout, account creation, email verification using otp, reset password, user profile, profile image upload with cropping while upload, edit profile, change password, follow/unfollow other users, etc. Stack: JavaScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, SemanticUI, MomentJS, Python, Flask, Jinja2, SQLAlchemy

CERTIFICATIONS

- (A) freeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design
- (A) freeCodeCamp Javascript Algorithms & Data Structures
- (A) freeCodeCamp Front-End Libraries
- (A) freeCodeCamp D₃ Data Visualization
- (A) freeCodeCamp APIs and Microservices
- (A) freeCodeCamp Scientific Computing with Python

Udemy Modern React with Redux

Udemy Python Bootcamp

AWARDS

Smart India Hackathon, 2018(Participated in GrandFinale) organized at Sir M. Visvesvaraya Institute of Technology by DRDO Bengaluru

Smart India Hackathon, 2017(Participated in GrandFinale) organized at Gujrat University Consortium by ISRO Ahmedabad

Won 1stPrize in Kavi Sammelan(Hindi Poetry) at Srishti 2016 InterCollege Techfest organized by LNCT Group, Bhopal

Won 2ndPrize in Chhatra Sansad(Group Debate) at Srishti 2016 InterCollege Techfest organized by LNCT Group, Bhopal